Hey, Dad, can I borrow 50000 dollors?
Mom needs kidney dialysis and we really don't have any money.
Natalie, the thing is...
How shameless have you to come here and beg us for money?
I'll pay you guys back, I promise.
Or maybe we can let her borrow the money.
I mean, it's her mother that's sick.
You're so thinking about your ex-wife?
No, no.
Do I need to remind you this is your family now? George,whitout me ,you have nothing
oh,ha, It isn't my loser sister?
Asking for money like a beggar, how pathetic.
This is a mistake.
wait!,we will give you the money.
What?
if！ You marry Sebastian Klein in my place.
oh，ho,ho, My daughter is so smart.
That's a good idea.
Sebastian Klein.
The legitimate son of the Klein family.
Isn't he in jail right now?
Yup.
He's a dirt bag and a good for nothing loser.
That's why I can't marry him.
That's right.
Natalie is also your daughter.
She can be the one who marries Sebastian Klein.
No, I'm not going to.
Do you want us to pay for your mother's medical bills or not?
Fine.
I'll marry Sebastian Klein.